Read
Are you really breaking things off?
Come on, lighten up.
Read
I don't get it.
Why's this happening?
Clearly, she wasn't happy about
Enomoto-san becoming the main model.
But why?
This is starting to piss me off!
Can a Boy-Girl Friendship Survive?
(No, It Can't!!)
Hydrangea and a New Seed
"Can't stop thinking about cute old me
now that we're not speaking?"
"You like me way too much, Yu!"
Or something like that.
Sure, she's cute.
But you know what?
What comes around goes around.
If that's how it is, then...
Man, spice and Yoghurppe
go together in such sweet harmony!
But I dunno if I can eat all this by myself.
If only there were someone to share it with.
So? What's bothering you?
She's actually planning to ignore me!
Fine then.
I guess we're not opening
a store together after all.
Did you hear that?
What a dick move.
Whatever's going on,
she didn't deserve that.
Damn that Himari magic!
This just looks like I'm bullying her.
Himari
Ms. Himari Inuzuka
Talent Agency Origin Production
Himari forwarded me an email?
"Thank you for joining our agency.
In preparation for your transfer
to Tokyo by the end of May,
we would like to visit your parents..."
No way!
You're joining a talent agency?
Bwa-ha!
Wha?!
She got me!
Hold up, Himari!
Dammit, she got away.
Yu-kun!
Hii-chan sent me this a second ago.
I'm going to Tokyo, so have fun with Yu!
Seriously?
I'm sorry, Yu-kun.
This all happened because I wanted to model.
No, it's not your fault at all.
We just need to find her and talk it out.
Here, I have just the thing.
Nice, homemade cookies!
That reminds me, I have her favorite drink.
I hope Hii-chan comes...
No way she can resist your awesome cookies.
I guarantee it'll work!
You two!
Don't think you can lure me
with sweets that easily!
I can see you hiding!
Hey!
Bam! Gotcha!
See, I knew you'd show up!
What an idiot.
Himari! Just hear me out.
Sh-Shut up!
I have nothing to talk to you about!
Liar! You've basically
been begging for attention!
No, I haven't!
Himari!
Yu-kun!
Wait up! Himari!
I said leave me alone!
What are you so upset about?
You're that mad about Enomoto-san modeling?
It's not about Enocchi!
You're the one who's pissing me off!
What? You can't be serious!
Science Room
How's it fair that I get juice poured on me?
Or that the entire class thinks I'm a dick?
Or that I get slapped out of nowhere?
Now you're going to Tokyo?
You could've at least talked to me about it.
Shows how little I mattered to you.
Was I just some toy for you to tease
and play with all this time?
Don't just stand there! Say something!
Stop!
Calm down!
I am calm!
Just let me go!
Listen to what I'm saying!
Sorry!
Move!
No way... It can't be...
Whatever.
I was just someone you could boss around.
Someone that made you accessories. Right?
I could say the same about you.
You only think of me as a convenient helper.
What? I don't think—
You don't?
Then why would you make
Enocchi your main model?
Why would you give someone else
the right to wear your accessories first?
You promised that role would be mine.
You like Enocchi, don't you?
That's why you're making
her your number one.
I get it. I know what love is.
I found out what it means.
I want to be happy for you two.
But... But...
There's no way I can be
happy as your second choice!
I'm going where there's
people who actually need me.
What are you doing out here?
Can you leave me alone?
I'm afraid not, buddy!
Rin-chan asked me to come check on you.
Why did you ask me to make
Enomoto-san the main model?
'Cause that seemed like the only
way she would stand a chance.
I can see why you'd root for her,
but that has nothing to do with modeling.
You really believe that?
The tricky thing about romance isn't
getting together, it's staying together.
What's the point if it'll fall apart?
That's especially
convincing coming from you.
What a shame if you and Rin-chan
begin dating, only for you to
parade around with Himari-chan
and make her the third wheel.
But Himari and I are best friends...
Then what's with all the agony?
"Like" and "love" aren't all that different.
Kind of like your new
feelings towards Himari-chan.
Otherwise, you'd have no reason
to avoid dating Rin-chan.
What's tripping you up is your guilt
from being attracted to Himari-chan.
It's time you put aside "romance"
or "friendship" or any of that.
What actually matters is that you
decide who's most important to you.
I'll admit, the whole
modeling thing with Rin-chan
was meant to tear you and Himari-chan apart.
But...
Himari-chan's decision to go
to Tokyo shows that
she could only move on from
you by leaving everything behind.
Who would've known she
had such strong feelings?
If Himari-chan actually leaves this way,
Rin-chan would blame herself.
I don't want my childhood friend
to go through that.
I'm not typically one to be so loyal.
You're actually a pretty nice person.
What?
N-No, I'm not!
Stop joking around.
You could forget Himari-chan and
just get with Rin-chan, you know.
Whatever, do what you want.
Let me remind you that Rin-chan would
make the best girlfriend you could find.
See, you're too nice.
You knew that if you put it like that,
I'd stop Himari from leaving.
Are you seriously going to Tokyo?
Yup.
Why?
So I can see my own worth.
See your worth...
Still as philosophical as ever, I see.
I doubt you'd understand.
Of course I do.
I've made accessories alone all these years.
No one understood me. Or even cared.
I wasn't needed by anyone.
But thanks to Himari,
my accessory-making career survived.
And they spread to others in the world.
So I promised to keep
making them for Himari.
If I turned my back on that promise,
it's only natural she leaves.
Can we scratch going to Tokyo?
Nope.
I'll bow down and apologize
about the modeling thing.
I know how stubborn Himari is.
She'll probably go to Tokyo
and become popular.
Whether I'm with her or not.
I guess it can't be helped.
It can't be helped.
Life doesn't always go your way.
And when it doesn't...
It's up to me to make my dream come true.
Bwa-ha!
Yu's such an idiot!
Like I'd ever go to Tokyo.
I'm not so desperate that I need to
satisfy my needs through
a bunch of strangers!
Well, my fake crying must have worked.
Yup, it was totally fake crying.
Why would I cry for real?
Yu's accessory broke, that's all.
Stop moping around!
You can get him to make you a new one!
I'll have him going, "Please, Himari-sama!"
And make him do whatever I want!
First, a monthly event called
"Thank you Himari-sama Day."
Second, he'll make me flower accessories!
And third, a kissing practice system.
Next time I ask for a practice kiss,
he can't refuse, no matter what!
I feel like I'm getting
off-topic, but oh well!
Tomorrow, Yu will bow down
and apologize to me.
Um?
Hello?
Why isn't he initiating?
Does he need time to cry
his eyes out from losing me?
Fine. Since you're cute,
I forgive you!
Hello, Sensei?
If I were to guess...
Yu will come crying to me over the weekend!
I know it!
Okay, I get it.
He must've been really upset
about the Tokyo thing.
Fine! Forgiven!
U-Um...
Maybe I'll peek
at his socials, just in case.
Huh?
That's Yu's hand.
It's like I actually
don't belong here anymore.
The new product launched already, too.
What if I really went to Tokyo?
When you do stuff like that,
it's kind of a drag.
Wake up, Himari!
You've already been dumped, remember?
There's no way he'd ask you to stay!
Hey, Himari. Home already?
Yup! Gotta study for exams!
Wow, you're working hard.
There's some curry on the
stove if you want some.
Okay!
Himari?
Hmm?
I see you haven't spoken
to Yu-kun in over a week.
Wanna fill me in?
You're wondering how I know.
It's very simple.
I can sense your "Yu-kun aura"
is rapidly declining.
So?
What happened?
You unbelievable dimwit!
You got dumped so you
threatened to move to Tokyo?
And now you're planning
on ordering him around?
That's called emotional blackmail!
You should be ashamed to be
a member of the Inuzuka family!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I'm sorry!
Himari, we have a deal, remember?
During that bazaar in middle school,
you begged me for a lifetime favor.
So to sell out 200 accessories,
I asked Enomoto to advertise them...
You made me beg Enomoto for help!
She forced me to bow down to her,
lick her heels, and sing in front of her!
I haven't even endured that
kind of humiliation at my job!
I-I get that you despise
Enocchi's big sister to death.
But I decided to help! Why?
Because his work spoke to me!
You remember our deal, right?
To never quit supporting Yu's
dream to open his own store.
Right you are!
Don't tell me that all this time...
You were only in it for fun and were
planning to abandon it when you got bored?
No, I swear! It's not like that!
Then what's this disaster about?
'C-Cause... I ended up falling for Yu!
Onii-chan, you don't get it at all!
What about my feelings?
I'm supposed to sacrifice myself?
That's right.
What's most important to you?
Is it romance? Or is it
having Yu-kun for yourself?
Aren't they the same?
Everything in life is finite.
You could have all the money in the world,
but that won't get you everything you want.
As a civil servant,
I worked on building highways.
That meant demolishing people's
homes and taking their land.
I've been met with more
criticism than gratitude.
But...
It was necessary for this town
to survive the next 100 years.
I'm doing work that will serve a purpose,
even after I die one day.
That's the kind of life I want for you, too.
Throw out the small stuff.
Work to grasp that one thing
that's important to you.
If you do that, you've won in life.
I couldn't fully understand
Onii-chan's point.
But I can't throw it all away now.
Not until I understand it but can't accept it.
Yu, can we talk?
It's important.
I have something to tell you, too.
Meet me in the science room.
It's not like a super big deal.
About that agency, it's well... um...
Ugh! I can't figure out what I wanna say!
A-Actually, could you go first?
I'll talk after you!
Oh, okay.
There's something I wanted to give you.
Notice of Withdrawal
From School
W-Withdrawal?!
Oh shit! Wrong one!
Sorry, that's not it! I messed up!
Hang on! Forget the mistake!
What's that notice for?
I'm thinking of quitting school.
I'll go to Tokyo. I'm coming with you.
Huh? W-With me?
Makishima told me to decide
what's most important to me.
And I decided it's you.
I'd need to figure out how
to make a living but...
Y-You mean... Wait.
You make it sound easy,
but if you start working,
you won't have as much time
to make accessories.
No flower accessory
is good enough without you!
But Himari, am I worth being
with if I can't make accessories?
Sure you are.
You're plenty!
I love watching videos together.
I love fighting over onion rings
on the way home from school.
I love going out together
on the train somewhere.
I love every minute I get to laugh with you!
Hey! What's that for?
Don't worry. I'm not going.
What? But you said you
want to feel needed by fans!
Y-You okay?
I did not say that!
And you're way too close!
Having your face so close makes me
want to go in for a kiss!
But I can't have my first
kiss be all sticky with juice!
You and I can go back to normal.
And I don't mind Enocchi modeling.
But could you keep me
as the... main model?
Sure.
So what did you wanna give me?
Wow...
Is this Anemone flaccida? It's so small.
I made it with a preserved Anemone flaccida.
A mini version.
A totally unique best
friend ring just for you.
I realized that you're my best friend.
I might make you mad again...
But it's not like other people
are more important than you.
I promise, that's the truth.
Yu, turn around for a sec.
Why?
Just do it!
Woot!
Hey! What are you doing?
Put it on for me?
Do it yourself.
No! I want you to do it!
Boo! Loser!
I told you, it's a best friend ring.
Bwa-ha!
Hey, what's this tiny thing?
It's an... Anemone flaccida seed.
Cool!
H-Hey.
You should just pick me.
If we're still alone at thirty, pick me.
Maybe, if I'm single then.
In the end, things are still the same.
But oh well.
If that's what Yu wants,
I can stay best friends.
I'll keep my feelings hidden in this ring.
Hey, Himari-san!
What's up?
Is it true that this is that
Natsume-kun you always hang out with?
How did it go?
Oh yeah. I haven't thanked her.
Thanks to you, it turned
out great. Thank you.
Glad I could help.
It took me some time to find it, though.
Pretty suave of you to sneak
in a purple tulip seed.
I bet Inuzuka-chan loved it.
How did she figure that out?
I can't tell Himari the meaning
behind purple tulips yet.
I'd die if I got dumped back there.
Someday, I'll tell her.
My best friend is too cute to handle.
A Hunk and Morning Glory Yutaka